You're seriously a calming presence.
And you're doing it again!
No, erm...
S... Sorry.
No, not sorry, but...
Um...
I'll go take a bath.
What?
Excuse me.
G-Getting down to it? I've already showered.
First, I'd like to ask your preferences.
Sorry, I got ahead of myself.
It makes me happy to see you're excited.
So I will call you "Akina".
Any play we do is up to my discretion,
and the massage to sex ratio will be 2:8.
Since these categories
may be embarrassing to verbalize,
please point to your answers, if possible.
[Experience: Different sorts of orgasms]
[Extra options: Toys, soft SM, SM]
Hardcore.
If you feel pressured,
you're free to tell me later.
No, I just appreciate how thorough you are
about confirming my preferences.
You truly are a pro.
Thank you.
When dining at a restaurant,
they always make sure
to ask for preferences, no?
I believe asking first is normal.
Normal...
You certainly aren't one
for emotional attachments.
You easy woman!
If you're fine with this price,
I'll go ahead and take a shower.
Go ahead.
Let us both enjoy our time together.
[Episode 4]
Sorry. I know you're only massaging me...
No worries. Please be at ease.
You have deft hands.
I'm glad to hear it.
May I embrace you?
Sure.
I will place your underwear on the table.
Huh? When did you...
I want this.
Not yet.
I'm sorry about the bed.
No worries. I placed a towel beneath us.
I've already changed the sheets as well.
Thorough indeed.
How was your first experience with me?
I always made fun of women
who said this phrase after having sex.
But I'll admit...
This really was a first for me.
My head went blank. I actually saw spots.
It wasn't like any mediocre sex
I've had before.
Even though you weren't done,
I kept feeling it in waves.
It felt so freeing to have someone else
do what they would with my body.
- I'm a bit miffed.
- Huh?
I'm the only one who really felt it.
But damn, it felt great.
[NAOKI]
If you choose to hire my services again,
call this number directly.
150 minutes on the dot.
Much obliged.
Your reactions were so cute,
I couldn't help but be aroused.
I will be seeing you again.
Good night.
Professionals are something else.
Morning.
Good morning.
No need to sound so stiff.
You're early today.
Yeah. I've got a recording to prep for.
I see.
Want some?
Right, you don't drink coffee.
Should I make you hot cocoa?
What now?
No, it's just... I didn't realize you knew.
What the... Of course I would know.
Right, of course.
Did you say something?
Nothing.
- I'll make the cocoa.
- It's fine, I'm already on it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Yum.
Hey, so...
I actually get off work early today.
Really? Nice.
What about you?
Me? I'm handling an interview,
but it should wrap up by 5:30PM.
Then when you're done...
how about we go grab dinner together?
You're making a mess!
I'll go.
I want to go.
Think about what you want to eat.
I'll give it some thought, too.
Okay.
Lost in her own world, again.
[NAOKI]
[He really eased my weary body.]
[An absolute professional!]
[His massage felt great.]
[He's not a licensed pro for nothing.]
Exactly.
They're all speaking the truth.
[NAOKI]
Did something good happen, Haru?
- Huh?
- You're practically beaming today.
Must have something to do with Ouji.
Well, you're not entirely wrong.
- Ouji embraced you?
- Stop!
Fuyumi, we're on the job right now!
Right, sorry. I lost my cool.
Your anecdotes are just so pure,
I can't help but react so excitedly.
Whoops, sorry.
But it was more a hug,
rather than an embrace.
Same difference.
The Ouji of before
would've kept his distance.
No wonder you're so happy.
When you put it that way...
Things are going well for you two after all.
It's like stocking up miles.
Sure, it's a slow grind.
But his love for me...
Is starting to pile up?
That's wonderful to hear.
With how long I had my one-sided crush,
I thought I was a long ways away
from mutual loving relationship.
Mutual loving relationship?
It's something Akina mentioned to me.
"You're not helping your case,
calling yourself a background extra."
"Why'd you even marry him
in the first place?"
She asks such scathing questions.
But right now, I feel like Ouji and I
aren't as far as I'd assumed.
If anything, you two are closer than ever.
Right? Mutual love isn't a dream, right?
Seems like you overcame one mountain.
I still have a ways to go.
Use your stocked miles,
and the trip will be a breeze.
Thanks for always humoring me.
Of course.
Is that why you introduced me to this gig?
As a show of appreciation?
No. no. But really, thanks for filling in.
The scheduled makeup artist caught the flu.
It's making the rounds again, isn't it?
But I appreciated the invitation.
I'm trying to increase my workload.
You are? Is your daughter
becoming more independent?
That, and my husband insisted.
Makes sense.
Your family truly is the golden standard
of a married relationship.
You think so?
I think a bit of ambiguity is key
to a healthy marriage though.
Ambiguity?
Excuse us.
- We're pleased to have you today.
- Likewise.
- I will be your stylist today.
- Thank you.
Please, have a seat.
[How about this store?]
Let's begin.
[Ouji: OK!]
Okay.
- Looking good.
- I'll be touching up.
Go ahead.
We're wrapping up early.
I'll head to the restaurant first.
Sounds good! Order something for youself.
I'll order my chicken skewers
when you get here.
You're free to eat before me.
Nah, I'll wait.
So hurry up and join me, okay?
Embrace each other, just like that.
Let me get another one.
Looking great, folks.
Thank you.
Thank you again.
Great work today. See you.
Just finished!
Great to hear!
- Thanks again.
- No, thank you.
- Take care!
- Night!
I'll hurry on over.
Take it slow, the food will still be here.
I'll hurry, slowly!
Be careful.
Things may be ambiguous and uncertain.
But if our relationship is changing,
ever so slightly...
I'm home.
Congrats!
Huh? For what?
You did work for a famous magazine today.
Congratulations.
I'm glad you were offered a worthwhile gig.
I was only filling in for a day.
Haru invited me to take the job.
Really? Haru did?
And here I thought
she only invited you to bars.
- What?
- She invites you out often, doesn't she?
It's like she doesn't know you have a child.
No, it's the other way around.
Huh?
Other way around?
She's a newlywed, remember?
So she looks to our marriage
as her ideal, and asks for advice.
Is that so?
Her husband was part of a band, right?
Yup.
Nowadays, he produces for other musicians.
- So he's a failure.
- Huh?
Our marriage will be of no reference to her.
Their standards are nothing close to ours.
"Standard"?
It means the accepted level for something.
What the general public thinks is good.
Loved you all day! Great work today!
What's so funny?
Nothing, sweetie.
Oh, right. Guess who's making
hamburger steaks for dinner tonight?
Welcome.
Haru. Over here.
You're out of breath. You ran, didn't you?
No, I speed-walked.
- One beer, please.
- Coming right up!
Suffragette is getting back together?
Yeah. Suzuki wants the band
to appear at a Summer Fest next year.
That's huge news!
It's really not.
But better now,
than after we gain beer bellies.
What a reason.
What's the set going to be?
I can't wait to see your outfits, too.
You're jumping the gun.
I can't help it!
Since you're so excited,
I guess I'll give it a go.
- I love him!
- What's wrong?
- Love...
- Huh?
I love t-this meat... this cut of meat.
Oh, the heart? Yeah, it's good.
Not pungent, either. I was really craving it.
Does this mean...
Let's pick back up from yesterday, shall we?
Haru?
What're you gonna order? Same thing?
Yeah, sounds good.
- Excuse me.
- No, I mustn't.
But it's possible.
It could definitely happen.
- And one shirako skewer.
- Sure thing.
Huh? Why am I daydreaming,
when the person I love
is right here, beside me?
This girl's head over heels for me.
I've always been like this.
I pushed while fearing rejection,
only for him to suddenly face my way.
Let's just get married.
But I pull the brakes
when things really matter.
I haven't managed to tell him anything.
I think a bit of ambiguity is key
to a healthy marriage though.
Forget ambiguity.
We haven't tried to understand each other.
It's freezing out here.
Hey now.
You're too old to be tripping, you...
I mean, Haruchan.
Here.
Thanks.
Up we go.
Ouji.
I...
I was happy.
What, about the band getting back together?
No, not that.
I was happy yesterday, when you hugged me.
And now, seeing you smile at me.
I'm really, really happy.
I never expected this from you,
Haru.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Since you act assertive,
but tend to hold your tongue.
- I'm surprised.
- Huh?
I never expected you to know my quirks.
Of course I'd know your quirks.
Right, of course.
Weirdo.
Wanna stop by the store?
- I know it's cold, but ice cream would...
- Ouji.
I...
I want to have sex with you.
[Preview]